{
    "N4L1KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "住む", "answer": "すむ", "english_answer": "to live" },
        { "question": "住民", "answer": "じゅうみん", "english_answer": "inhabitants" },
        { "question": "所", "answer": "ところ", "english_answer": "place" },
        { "question": "住所", "answer": "じゅうしょ", "english_answer": "address" },
        { "question": "台所", "answer": "だいどころ", "english_answer": "kitchen" },
        { "question": "場所", "answer": "ばしょ", "english_answer": "place" },
        { "question": "東京", "answer": "とうきょう", "english_answer": "Tokyo" },
        { "question": "東京都", "answer": "とうきょうと", "english_answer": "metropolis of Tokyo" },
        { "question": "都合がいい", "answer": "つごうがいい", "english_answer": "convenient" },
        { "question": "首都", "answer": "しゅと", "english_answer": "capital" },
        { "question": "京都府", "answer": "きょうとふ", "english_answer": "Kyoto Prefecture" },
        { "question": "大阪府", "answer": "おおさかふ", "english_answer": "Osaka Prefecture" },
        { "question": "政府", "answer": "せいふ", "english_answer": "government" },
        { "question": "山口県", "answer": "やまぐちけん", "english_answer": "Yamaguchi Prefecture" },
        { "question": "県知事", "answer": "けんちじ", "english_answer": "prefectural governor" },
        { "question": "京都市", "answer": "きょうとし", "english_answer": "Kyoto City" },
        { "question": "市長", "answer": "しちょう", "english_answer": "mayor" },
        { "question": "市場", "answer": "いちば", "english_answer": "market" },
        { "question": "北区", "answer": "きたく", "english_answer": "Kita Ward" },
        { "question": "文京区", "answer": "ぶんきょうく", "english_answer": "Bunkyo Ward" },
        { "question": "区長", "answer": "くちょう", "english_answer": "ward mayor" },
        { "question": "町", "answer": "まち", "english_answer": "town" },
        { "question": "下町", "answer": "したまち", "english_answer": "downtown" },
        { "question": "町長", "answer": "ちょうちょう", "english_answer": "town leader" },
        { "question": "村", "answer": "むら", "english_answer": "village" },
        { "question": "村人", "answer": "むらびと", "english_answer": "villager" },
        { "question": "村長", "answer": "そんちょう", "english_answer": "village leader" }
    ],
    "N4L2KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "明るい", "answer": "あかるい", "english_answer": "bright, cheerful" },
        { "question": "明日", "answer": "あした、あす", "english_answer": "tomorrow" },
        { "question": "説明", "answer": "せつめい", "english_answer": "explanation" },
        { "question": "発明", "answer": "はつめい", "english_answer": "invention" },
        { "question": "暗い", "answer": "くらい", "english_answer": "dark" },
        { "question": "暗号", "answer": "あんごう", "english_answer": "secret code" },
        { "question": "遠い", "answer": "とおい", "english_answer": "far" },
        { "question": "遠足", "answer": "えんそく", "english_answer": "excursion" },
        { "question": "近い", "answer": "ちかい", "english_answer": "near" },
        { "question": "近所", "answer": "きんじょ", "english_answer": "neighborhood" },
        { "question": "最近", "answer": "さいきん", "english_answer": "recently" },
        { "question": "強い", "answer": "つよい", "english_answer": "strong" },
        { "question": "勉強する", "answer": "べんきょうする", "english_answer": "to study" },
        { "question": "強風", "answer": "ききょうふう", "english_answer": "big wind" },
        { "question": "弱い", "answer": "よわい", "english_answer": "weak" },
        { "question": "強弱", "answer": "きょうじゃく", "english_answer": "strong and weak" },
        { "question": "重い", "answer": "おもい", "english_answer": "heavy" },
        { "question": "重大な", "answer": "じゅうだいな", "english_answer": "important" },
        { "question": "体重", "answer": "たいじゅう", "english_answer": "body weight" },
        { "question": "軽い", "answer": "かるい", "english_answer": "light" },
        { "question": "軽食", "answer": "けいしょく", "english_answer": "snack" },
        { "question": "太い", "answer": "ふとい", "english_answer": "fat" },
        { "question": "太陽", "answer": "たいよう", "english_answer": "sun" },
        { "question": "細い", "answer": "ほそい", "english_answer": "slender" },
        { "question": "細かい", "answer": "こまかい", "english_answer": "fine" },
        { "question": "細工", "answer": "さいく", "english_answer": "craftmanship" }
    ],
    "N4L3KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "特に", "answer": "とくに", "english_answer": "especially" },
        { "question": "特急", "answer": "とっきゅう", "english_answer": "limited express" },
        { "question": "別れる", "answer": "わかれる", "english_answer": "separate" },
        { "question": "別々に", "answer": "べつべつに", "english_answer": "separately" },
        { "question": "区別する", "answer": "くべつする", "english_answer": "distinguish" },
        { "question": "分別する", "answer": "ぶんべつする", "english_answer": "classify" },
        { "question": "有る", "answer": "ある", "english_answer": "to exist, to be" },
        { "question": "有名な", "answer": "ゆうめいな", "english_answer": "famous" },
        { "question": "有料", "answer": "ゆうりょう", "english_answer": "pay toll" },
        { "question": "便り", "answer": "たより", "english_answer": "letter" },
        { "question": "郵便局", "answer": "ゆうびんきょく", "english_answer": "post office" },
        { "question": "船便", "answer": "ふなびん", "english_answer": "sea mail" },
        { "question": "便利な", "answer": "べんりな", "english_answer": "convenient" },
        { "question": "利用する", "answer": "りようする", "english_answer": "to use" },
        { "question": "利子", "answer": "りし", "english_answer": "interest" },
        { "question": "有利な", "answer": "ゆうりな", "english_answer": "advantageous" },
        { "question": "不便な", "answer": "ふべんな", "english_answer": "inconvenient" },
        { "question": "不足する", "answer": "ふそくする", "english_answer": "run short" },
        { "question": "不安な", "answer": "ふあんな", "english_answer": "anxious" },
        { "question": "不運な", "answer": "ふうんな", "english_answer": "unfortunate" },
        { "question": "切る", "answer": "きる", "english_answer": "to cut" },
        { "question": "切手", "answer": "きって", "english_answer": "postage stamp" },
        { "question": "大切な", "answer": "たいせつな", "english_answer": "important" },
        { "question": "親切な", "answer": "しんせつな", "english_answer": "kind" },
        { "question": "元気な", "answer": "げんきな", "english_answer": "fine, active" },
        { "question": "元日", "answer": "がんじつ", "english_answer": "New Year's Day" },
        { "question": "紀元前", "answer": "きげんぜん", "english_answer": "before Christ" },
        { "question": "好きな", "answer": "すきな", "english_answer": "favorite" },
        { "question": "好意", "answer": "こうい", "english_answer": "affection" },
        { "question": "好物", "answer": "こうぶつ", "english_answer": "favorite dish" },
        { "question": "急に", "answer": "きゅうに", "english_answer": "suddenly" },
        { "question": "特急", "answer": "とっきゅう", "english_answer": "limited express" },
        { "question": "急ぐ", "answer": "いそぐ", "english_answer": "hurry" },
        { "question": "急用", "answer": "きゅうよう", "english_answer": "urgent business" }
    ],
    "N4L4KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "低い", "answer": "ひくい", "english_answer": "low" },
        { "question": "低下する", "answer": "ていかする", "english_answer": "to fall" },
        { "question": "低気圧", "answer": "ていきあつ", "english_answer": "low pressure" },
        { "question": "広い", "answer": "ひろい", "english_answer": "spacious" },
        { "question": "広場", "answer": "ひろば", "english_answer": "plaza" },
        { "question": "広大な", "answer": "こうだいな", "english_answer": "vast" },
        { "question": "短い", "answer": "みじかい", "english_answer": "short" },
        { "question": "短時間", "answer": "たんじかん", "english_answer": "short time" },
        { "question": "良い", "answer": "よい", "english_answer": "good" },
        { "question": "良心", "answer": "りょうしん", "english_answer": "conscience" },
        { "question": "悪い", "answer": "わるい", "english_answer": "bad" },
        { "question": "悪人", "answer": "あくにん", "english_answer": "bad person" },
        { "question": "正しい", "answer": "ただしい", "english_answer": "correct, right" },
        { "question": "正月", "answer": "しょうがつ", "english_answer": "the New Year" },
        { "question": "正門", "answer": "せいもん", "english_answer": "main gate" },
        { "question": "変わる", "answer": "かわる", "english_answer": "to change" },
        { "question": "変な", "answer": "へんな", "english_answer": "strange" },
        { "question": "大変な", "answer": "たいへんな", "english_answer": "hard" },
        { "question": "変化する", "answer": "へんかする", "english_answer": "to change" },
        { "question": "赤い", "answer": "あかい", "english_answer": "red" },
        { "question": "赤ちゃん", "answer": "あかちゃん", "english_answer": "baby" },
        { "question": "赤信号", "answer": "あかしんごう", "english_answer": "red light" },
        { "question": "赤道", "answer": "せきどう", "english_answer": "equator" },
        { "question": "青い", "answer": "あおい", "english_answer": "blue" },
        { "question": "青空", "answer": "あおぞら", "english_answer": "blue sky" },
        { "question": "青春", "answer": "せいしゅん", "english_answer": "youth" },
        { "question": "黒い", "answer": "くろい", "english_answer": "black" },
        { "question": "真っ黒", "answer": "まっくろ", "english_answer": "pitch black" }
    ],
    "N4L5KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "映す", "answer": "うつす", "english_answer": "to reflect" },
        { "question": "映画", "answer": "えいが", "english_answer": "movie" },
        { "question": "映画館", "answer": "えいがかん", "english_answer": "movie theater" },
        { "question": "計画", "answer": "けいかく", "english_answer": "plan" },
        { "question": "画家", "answer": "がか", "english_answer": "painter" },
        { "question": "日本画", "answer": "にほんが", "english_answer": "Japanese painting" },
        { "question": "音", "answer": "おと", "english_answer": "sound" },
        { "question": "発音", "answer": "はつおん", "english_answer": "pronunciation" },
        { "question": "高音", "answer": "こうおん", "english_answer": "high note" },
        { "question": "楽しい", "answer": "たのしい", "english_answer": "enjoyable" },
        { "question": "音楽", "answer": "おんがく", "english_answer": "music" },
        { "question": "楽な", "answer": "らくな", "english_answer": "easy" },
        { "question": "歌う", "answer": "うたう", "english_answer": "to sing" },
        { "question": "歌手", "answer": "かしゅ", "english_answer": "singer" },
        { "question": "写真", "answer": "しゃしん", "english_answer": "a photograph" },
        { "question": "写す", "answer": "うつす", "english_answer": "to copy" },
        { "question": "真ん中", "answer": "まんなか", "english_answer": "midmost" },
        { "question": "真っ白", "answer": "まっしろ", "english_answer": "pure white" },
        { "question": "真実", "answer": "しんじつ", "english_answer": "truth" },
        { "question": "旅行する", "answer": "りょこうする", "english_answer": "to take a trip" },
        { "question": "旅館", "answer": "りょかん", "english_answer": "Japanese-style hotel" },
        { "question": "旅", "answer": "たび", "english_answer": "trip" },
        { "question": "世話をする", "answer": "せわをする", "english_answer": "to take care of" },
        { "question": "世の中", "answer": "よのなか", "english_answer": "world, society" },
        { "question": "２１世紀", "answer": "２１せいき", "english_answer": "21st century" },
        { "question": "世界", "answer": "せかい", "english_answer": "world" },
        { "question": "政界", "answer": "せいかい", "english_answer": "political world" }
    ],
    "N4L6KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "仕事", "answer": "しごと", "english_answer": "job" },
        { "question": "仕方がない", "answer": "しかたがない", "english_answer": "there is no choice" },
        { "question": "火事", "answer": "かじ", "english_answer": "fire" },
        { "question": "用事", "answer": "ようじ", "english_answer": "business" },
        { "question": "大事な", "answer": "だいじな", "english_answer": "important" },
        { "question": "事", "answer": "こと", "english_answer": "matter" },
        { "question": "銀行", "answer": "ぎんこう", "english_answer": "bank" },
        { "question": "銀", "answer": "ぎん", "english_answer": "silver" },
        { "question": "銀座", "answer": "ぎんざ", "english_answer": "Ginza (place)" },
        { "question": "会社員", "answer": "かいしゃいん", "english_answer": "employee of a company" },
        { "question": "銀行員", "answer": "ぎんこういん", "english_answer": "bank clerk" },
        { "question": "店員", "answer": "てんいん", "english_answer": "clerk" },
        { "question": "会員", "answer": "かいいん", "english_answer": "membership" },
        { "question": "医者", "answer": "いしゃ", "english_answer": "doctor" },
        { "question": "医学", "answer": "いがく", "english_answer": "medical science" },
        { "question": "医院", "answer": "いいん", "english_answer": "doctor's office" },
        { "question": "者", "answer": "もの", "english_answer": "person" },
        { "question": "歯医者", "answer": "はいしゃ", "english_answer": "dentist" },
        { "question": "学者", "answer": "がくしゃ", "english_answer": "scholar" },
        { "question": "作者", "answer": "さくしゃ", "english_answer": "author" },
        { "question": "働く", "answer": "はたらく", "english_answer": "to work" },
        { "question": "労働者", "answer": "ろうどうしゃ", "english_answer": "laborer, worker" },
        { "question": "本屋", "answer": "ほんや", "english_answer": "bookstore" },
        { "question": "屋上", "answer": "おくじょう", "english_answer": "roof, housetop" },
        { "question": "八百屋", "answer": "やおや", "english_answer": "grocery" },
        { "question": "部屋", "answer": "へや", "english_answer": "room" },
        { "question": "産む", "answer": "うむ", "english_answer": "to give birth" },
        { "question": "生産する", "answer": "せいさんする", "english_answer": "to produce" },
        { "question": "財産", "answer": "ざいさん", "english_answer": "fortune" },
        { "question": "産業", "answer": "さんぎょう", "english_answer": "industry" },
        { "question": "工業", "answer": "こうぎょう", "english_answer": "manufacture" },
        { "question": "授業", "answer": "じゅぎょう", "english_answer": "class, lesson" },
        { "question": "本日休業", "answer": "ほんじつきゅうぎょう", "english_answer": "closed today" }
    ],
    "N4L7KQuiz": [
        { "question": "林", "answer": "はやし", "english_answer": "wood, grove" },
        { "question": "小林さん", "answer": "こばやしさん", "english_answer": "Mr. or Ms. Kobayashi" },
        { "question": "林道", "answer": "りんどう", "english_answer": "forest road" },
        { "question": "森", "answer": "もり", "english_answer": "forest" },
        { "question": "森さん", "answer": "もりさん", "english_answer": "Mr. or Ms. Mori" },
        { "question": "森林", "answer": "しんりん", "english_answer": "forest" },
        { "question": "地図", "answer": "ちず", "english_answer": "map" },
        { "question": "地下鉄", "answer": "ちかてつ", "english_answer": "subway" },
        { "question": "土地", "answer": "とち", "english_answer": "land" },
        { "question": "地震", "answer": "じしん", "english_answer": "earthquake" },
        { "question": "池", "answer": "いけ", "english_answer": "pond" },
        { "question": "電池", "answer": "でんち", "english_answer": "battery" },
        { "question": "海", "answer": "うみ", "english_answer": "the sea, the ocean" },
        { "question": "海外", "answer": "かいがい", "english_answer": "overseas" },
        { "question": "北海道", "answer": "ほっかいどう", "english_answer": "Hokkaido" },
        { "question": "西洋", "answer": "せいよう", "english_answer": "the West" },
        { "question": "東洋", "answer": "とうよう", "english_answer": "the East" },
        { "question": "洋服", "answer": "ようふく", "english_answer": "clothes" },
        { "question": "大西洋", "answer": "たいせいよう", "english_answer": "the Atlantic (Ocean)" },
        { "question": "雪", "answer": "ゆき", "english_answer": "snow" },
        { "question": "大雪", "answer": "おおゆき", "english_answer": "heavy snow" },
        { "question": "新雪", "answer": "しんせつ", "english_answer": "fresh snow" },
        { "question": "光", "answer": "ひかり", "english_answer": "light" },
        { "question": "光る", "answer": "ひかる", "english_answer": "to shine" },
        { "question": "日光", "answer": "にっこう", "english_answer": "sunlight" },
        { "question": "観光", "answer": "かんこう", "english_answer": "sightseeing" },
        { "question": "台", "answer": "だい", "english_answer": "table" },
        { "question": "台所", "answer": "だいどころ", "english_answer": "kitchen" },
        { "question": "～台", "answer": "～だい", "english_answer": "counter for machines" },
        { "question": "土台", "answer": "どだい", "english_answer": "foundation" },
        { "question": "風", "answer": "かぜ", "english_answer": "wind" },
        { "question": "台風", "answer": "たいふう", "english_answer": "typhoon" },
        { "question": "洋風", "answer": "ようふう", "english_answer": "western style" },
        { "question": "風景", "answer": "ふうけい", "english_answer": "scenery" }
    ],
    "N4L8KQuiz": [
        { "question": "四季", "answer": "しき", "english_answer": "four seasons" },
        { "question": "季節", "answer": "きせつ", "english_answer": "season" },
        { "question": "節分", "answer": "せつぶん", "english_answer": "the traditional end of winter" },
        { "question": "春", "answer": "はる", "english_answer": "spring" },
        { "question": "青春", "answer": "せいしゅん", "english_answer": "youth" },
        { "question": "夏", "answer": "なつ", "english_answer": "summer" },
        { "question": "夏休み", "answer": "なつやすみ", "english_answer": "summer holidays" },
        { "question": "夏まつり", "answer": "なつまつり", "english_answer": "summer festival" },
        { "question": "夏服", "answer": "なつふく", "english_answer": "summer clothes" },
        { "question": "秋", "answer": "あき", "english_answer": "autumn" },
        { "question": "秋田県", "answer": "あきたけん", "english_answer": "Akita Prefecture" },
        { "question": "秋分の日", "answer": "しゅうぶんのひ", "english_answer": "Autumnal Equinox Day" },
        { "question": "冬", "answer": "ふゆ", "english_answer": "winter" },
        { "question": "冬休み", "answer": "ふゆやすみ", "english_answer": "winter holidays" },
        { "question": "春夏秋冬", "answer": "しゅんかしゅうとう", "english_answer": "spring, summer, autumn, winter" },
        { "question": "暑い", "answer": "あつい", "english_answer": "hot" },
        { "question": "残暑", "answer": "ざんしょ", "english_answer": "late-summer heat" },
        { "question": "寒い", "answer": "さむい", "english_answer": "cold" },
        { "question": "寒波", "answer": "かんぱ", "english_answer": "cold wave" },
        { "question": "暖かい", "answer": "あたたかい", "english_answer": "warm" },
        { "question": "暖冬", "answer": "だんとう", "english_answer": "warm winter" },
        { "question": "暖房", "answer": "だんぼう", "english_answer": "heating" },
        { "question": "温暖化", "answer": "おんだんか", "english_answer": "warming" },
        { "question": "涼しい", "answer": "すずしい", "english_answer": "cool" },
        { "question": "涼風", "answer": "りょうふう", "english_answer": "cool breeze" }
    ],
    "N4L9KQuiz": [
        { "question": "体", "answer": "からだ", "english_answer": "body" },
        { "question": "体力", "answer": "たいりょく", "english_answer": "physical strength" },
        { "question": "体重", "answer": "たいじゅう", "english_answer": "body weight" },
        { "question": "頭", "answer": "あたま", "english_answer": "head" },
        { "question": "頭がいい", "answer": "あたまがいい", "english_answer": "smart" },
        { "question": "頭痛", "answer": "ずつう", "english_answer": "headache" },
        { "question": "顔", "answer": "かお", "english_answer": "face" },
        { "question": "顔色", "answer": "かおいろ", "english_answer": "complexion" },
        { "question": "首", "answer": "くび", "english_answer": "neck" },
        { "question": "首都", "answer": "しゅと", "english_answer": "capital" },
        { "question": "手首", "answer": "てくび", "english_answer": "wrist" },
        { "question": "首相", "answer": "しゅしょう", "english_answer": "prime minister" },
        { "question": "心", "answer": "こころ", "english_answer": "heart" },
        { "question": "安心する", "answer": "あんしんする", "english_answer": "to be relieved" },
        { "question": "心配する", "answer": "しんぱいする", "english_answer": "to worry" },
        { "question": "中心", "answer": "ちゅうしん", "english_answer": "center" },
        { "question": "声", "answer": "こえ", "english_answer": "voice" },
        { "question": "大声", "answer": "おおごえ", "english_answer": "loud voice" },
        { "question": "病気", "answer": "びょうき", "english_answer": "illness" },
        { "question": "病院", "answer": "びょういん", "english_answer": "hospital" },
        { "question": "病人", "answer": "びょうにん", "english_answer": "sick person" },
        { "question": "急病", "answer": "きゅうびょう", "english_answer": "sudden illness" },
        { "question": "薬", "answer": "くすり", "english_answer": "medicine" },
        { "question": "目薬", "answer": "めぐすり", "english_answer": "eye lotion" },
        { "question": "薬品", "answer": "やくひん", "english_answer": "medicine" },
        { "question": "科学", "answer": "かがく", "english_answer": "science" },
        { "question": "教科書", "answer": "きょうかしょ", "english_answer": "textbook" },
        { "question": "外科", "answer": "げか", "english_answer": "surgery" },
        { "question": "内側", "answer": "うちがわ", "english_answer": "inside" },
        { "question": "内科", "answer": "ないか", "english_answer": "internal medicine" },
        { "question": "車内", "answer": "しゃない", "english_answer": "in the car" },
        { "question": "案内する", "answer": "あんないする", "english_answer": "to guide" }
    ],
    "N4L10KQuiz": [
        { "question": "朝", "answer": "あさ", "english_answer": "morning" },
        { "question": "今朝", "answer": "けさ", "english_answer": "this morning" },
        { "question": "朝日", "answer": "あさひ", "english_answer": "the morning sun" },
        { "question": "朝食", "answer": "ちょうしょく", "english_answer": "breakfast" },
        { "question": "昼", "answer": "ひる", "english_answer": "noon" },
        { "question": "昼休み", "answer": "ひるやすみ", "english_answer": "lunch break" },
        { "question": "昼ご飯", "answer": "ひるごはん", "english_answer": "lunch" },
        { "question": "昼食", "answer": "ちゅうしょく", "english_answer": "lunch" },
        { "question": "夜", "answer": "よる", "english_answer": "night" },
        { "question": "今夜", "answer": "こんや", "english_answer": "tonight" },
        { "question": "夜店", "answer": "よみせ", "english_answer": "night stall" },
        { "question": "夜食", "answer": "やしょく", "english_answer": "bedtime snack" },
        { "question": "夕日", "answer": "ゆうひ", "english_answer": "sunset" },
        { "question": "夕食", "answer": "ゆうしょく", "english_answer": "supper" },
        { "question": "七夕", "answer": "たなばた", "english_answer": "Star Festival" },
        { "question": "読み方", "answer": "よみかた", "english_answer": "how to read" },
        { "question": "夕方", "answer": "ゆうがた", "english_answer": "evening" },
        { "question": "あの方", "answer": "あのかた", "english_answer": "that person" },
        { "question": "方法", "answer": "ほうほう", "english_answer": "method" },
        { "question": "今晩", "answer": "こんばん", "english_answer": "tonight" },
        { "question": "毎晩", "answer": "まいばん", "english_answer": "every night" },
        { "question": "晩ご飯", "answer": "ばんごはん", "english_answer": "dinner" },
        { "question": "時計", "answer": "とけい", "english_answer": "watch, clock" },
        { "question": "計画", "answer": "けいかく", "english_answer": "plan" },
        { "question": "計る", "answer": "はかる", "english_answer": "to measure" },
        { "question": "合計", "answer": "ごうけい", "english_answer": "total" },
        { "question": "日曜日", "answer": "にちようび", "english_answer": "Sunday" },
        { "question": "水曜日", "answer": "すいようび", "english_answer": "Wednesday" },
        { "question": "何曜日", "answer": "なんようび", "english_answer": "what day of the week" },
        { "question": "以上", "answer": "いじょう", "english_answer": "more than" },
        { "question": "以下", "answer": "いか", "english_answer": "less than" },
        { "question": "以外", "answer": "いがい", "english_answer": "except" },
        { "question": "以前", "answer": "いぜん", "english_answer": "previously" },
        { "question": "一度", "answer": "いちど", "english_answer": "once" },
        { "question": "今度", "answer": "こんど", "english_answer": "next time" },
        { "question": "２５度", "answer": "２５ど", "english_answer": "25 degrees" },
        { "question": "温度", "answer": "おんど", "english_answer": "temperature" }
    ],
    "N4L11KQuiz": [
        { "question": "止まる", "answer": "とまる", "english_answer": "to stop" },
        { "question": "中止する", "answer": "ちゅうしする", "english_answer": "to call off" },
        { "question": "一時停止", "answer": "いちじていし", "english_answer": "stop sign" },
        { "question": "歩く", "answer": "あるく", "english_answer": "to walk" },
        { "question": "散歩する", "answer": "さんぽする", "english_answer": "to take a walk" },
        { "question": "進歩する", "answer": "しんぽする", "english_answer": "to make progress" },
        { "question": "横断歩道", "answer": "おうだんほどう", "english_answer": "crosswalk" },
        { "question": "走る", "answer": "はしる", "english_answer": "to run" },
        { "question": "力走する", "answer": "りきそうする", "english_answer": "to run as fast as possible" },
        { "question": "起きる", "answer": "おきる", "english_answer": "to get up" },
        { "question": "早起き", "answer": "はやおき", "english_answer": "early riser" },
        { "question": "起業家", "answer": "きぎょうか", "english_answer": "enterpreneur" },
        { "question": "持つ", "answer": "もつ", "english_answer": "to hold" },
        { "question": "気持ち", "answer": "きもち", "english_answer": "feeling" },
        { "question": "持ち物", "answer": "もちもの", "english_answer": "belongings" },
        { "question": "支持する", "answer": "しじする", "english_answer": "to support" },
        { "question": "待つ", "answer": "まつ", "english_answer": "to wait" },
        { "question": "待ち合わせ", "answer": "まちあわせ", "english_answer": "rendezvous" },
        { "question": "招待する", "answer": "しょうたいする", "english_answer": "to invite" },
        { "question": "期待する", "answer": "きたいする", "english_answer": "to hope" },
        { "question": "借りる", "answer": "かりる", "english_answer": "to borrow" },
        { "question": "借金", "answer": "しゃっきん", "english_answer": "debt" },
        { "question": "貸す", "answer": "かす", "english_answer": "to lend" },
        { "question": "貸家", "answer": "かしや", "english_answer": "house for rent" },
        { "question": "賃貸マンション", "answer": "ちんたいマンション", "english_answer": "rented apartment" },
        { "question": "始める", "answer": "はじめる", "english_answer": "to begin" },
        { "question": "開始する", "answer": "かいしする", "english_answer": "to start" },
        { "question": "始発", "answer": "しはつ", "english_answer": "first train" },
        { "question": "終わる", "answer": "おわる", "english_answer": "to end" },
        { "question": "終電", "answer": "しゅうでん", "english_answer": "last train" },
        { "question": "最終回", "answer": "さいしゅうかい", "english_answer": "final episode" }
    ],
    "N4L12KQuiz": [
        { "question": "家", "answer": "いえ", "english_answer": "house" },
        { "question": "画家", "answer": "がか", "english_answer": "painter" },
        { "question": "家内", "answer": "かない", "english_answer": "wife" },
        { "question": "家庭", "answer": "かてい", "english_answer": "family" },
        { "question": "家族", "answer": "かぞく", "english_answer": "family" },
        { "question": "民族", "answer": "みんぞく", "english_answer": "race" },
        { "question": "水族館", "answer": "すいぞくかん", "english_answer": "aquarium" },
        { "question": "私", "answer": "わたし", "english_answer": "I" },
        { "question": "私立大学", "answer": "しりつだいがく", "english_answer": "private university" },
        { "question": "私生活", "answer": "しせいかつ", "english_answer": "private life" },
        { "question": "自分", "answer": "じぶん", "english_answer": "oneself" },
        { "question": "自動ドア", "answer": "じどうドア", "english_answer": "automatic door" },
        { "question": "自由", "answer": "じゆう", "english_answer": "freedom" },
        { "question": "自然", "answer": "しぜん", "english_answer": "nature" },
        { "question": "親", "answer": "おや", "english_answer": "parent" },
        { "question": "母親", "answer": "ははおや", "english_answer": "mother" },
        { "question": "親切な", "answer": "しんせつな", "english_answer": "kind" },
        { "question": "親しい", "answer": "したしい", "english_answer": "close" },
        { "question": "両親", "answer": "りょうしん", "english_answer": "parents" },
        { "question": "両方", "answer": "りょうほう", "english_answer": "both" },
        { "question": "両手", "answer": "りょうて", "english_answer": "both hands" },
        { "question": "両替え", "answer": "りょうがえ", "english_answer": "money exchange" },
        { "question": "兄", "answer": "あに", "english_answer": "one's elder brother" },
        { "question": "お兄さん", "answer": "おにいさん", "english_answer": "elder brother" },
        { "question": "弟", "answer": "おとうと", "english_answer": "one's younger brother" },
        { "question": "兄弟", "answer": "きょうだい", "english_answer": "brothers" },
        { "question": "姉", "answer": "あね", "english_answer": "one's elder sister" },
        { "question": "お姉さん", "answer": "おねえさん", "english_answer": "elder sister" },
        { "question": "妹", "answer": "いもうと", "english_answer": "one's younger sister" },
        { "question": "姉妹", "answer": "しまい", "english_answer": "sisters" },
        { "question": "姉妹都市", "answer": "しまいとし", "english_answer": "sister city" }
    ],
    "N4L13KQuiz": [
        { "question": "生活", "answer": "せいかつ", "english_answer": "living" },
        { "question": "活動", "answer": "かつどう", "english_answer": "activity" },
        { "question": "活発な", "answer": "かっぱつな", "english_answer": "active" },
        { "question": "回す", "answer": "まわす", "english_answer": "to turn" },
        { "question": "一回", "answer": "いっかい", "english_answer": "once" },
        { "question": "前回", "answer": "ぜんかい", "english_answer": "the last time" },
        { "question": "回転ずし", "answer": "かいてんずし", "english_answer": "coveyor-belt sushi" },
        { "question": "主人", "answer": "しゅじん", "english_answer": "husband" },
        { "question": "主食", "answer": "しゅしょく", "english_answer": "staple food" },
        { "question": "主な", "answer": "おもな", "english_answer": "main" },
        { "question": "持ち主", "answer": "もちぬし", "english_answer": "owner" },
        { "question": "色", "answer": "いろ", "english_answer": "color" },
        { "question": "茶色", "answer": "ちゃいろ", "english_answer": "brown" },
        { "question": "特色", "answer": "とくしょく", "english_answer": "characteristic" },
        { "question": "景色", "answer": "けしき", "english_answer": "scenery" },
        { "question": "形", "answer": "かたち", "english_answer": "shape" },
        { "question": "人形", "answer": "にんぎょう", "english_answer": "doll" },
        { "question": "正方形", "answer": "せいほうけい", "english_answer": "square" },
        { "question": "図形", "answer": "ずけい", "english_answer": "figure" },
        { "question": "品物", "answer": "しなもの", "english_answer": "goods" },
        { "question": "食料品", "answer": "しょくりょうひん", "english_answer": "food" },
        { "question": "電気製品", "answer": "でんきせいひん", "english_answer": "electrical appliance" },
        { "question": "作品", "answer": "さくひん", "english_answer": "piece of work" },
        { "question": "国民", "answer": "こくみん", "english_answer": "citizens of the state" },
        { "question": "市民", "answer": "しみん", "english_answer": "citizen" },
        { "question": "民族", "answer": "みんぞく", "english_answer": "tribe" },
        { "question": "民主主義", "answer": "みんしゅしゅぎ", "english_answer": "democracy" },
        { "question": "服", "answer": "ふく", "english_answer": "clothes" },
        { "question": "洋服", "answer": "ようふく", "english_answer": "Western clothing" },
        { "question": "和服", "answer": "わふく", "english_answer": "Japanese clothing" },
        { "question": "制服", "answer": "せいふく", "english_answer": "uniform" },
        { "question": "犬", "answer": "いぬ", "english_answer": "dog" },
        { "question": "子犬", "answer": "こいぬ", "english_answer": "puppy" },
        { "question": "日本犬", "answer": "にほんけん", "english_answer": "Japanese dog" },
        { "question": "同じ", "answer": "おなじ", "english_answer": "same" },
        { "question": "同時に", "answer": "どうじに", "english_answer": "at the same time" },
        { "question": "同級生", "answer": "どうきゅうせい", "english_answer": "classmate" }
    ],
    "N4L14KQuiz": [
        { "question": "米", "answer": "こめ", "english_answer": "rice" },
        { "question": "米国", "answer": "べいこく", "english_answer": "U.S.A" },
        { "question": "白米", "answer": "はくまい", "english_answer": "polished rice" },
        { "question": "料金", "answer": "りょうきん", "english_answer": "fee, charge" },
        { "question": "食料品", "answer": "しょくりょうひん", "english_answer": "foods" },
        { "question": "資料", "answer": "しりょう", "english_answer": "documents, data" },
        { "question": "材料", "answer": "ざいりょう", "english_answer": "materials" },
        { "question": "料理", "answer": "りょうり", "english_answer": "cooking" },
        { "question": "地理", "answer": "ちり", "english_answer": "geography" },
        { "question": "無理な", "answer": "むりな", "english_answer": "impossible" },
        { "question": "理由", "answer": "りゆう", "english_answer": "reason" },
        { "question": "肉", "answer": "にく", "english_answer": "meat" },
        { "question": "牛肉", "answer": "ぎゅうにく", "english_answer": "beef" },
        { "question": "肉屋", "answer": "にくや", "english_answer": "butcher" },
        { "question": "筋肉", "answer": "きんにく", "english_answer": "muscle" },
        { "question": "鳥", "answer": "とり", "english_answer": "bird" },
        { "question": "小鳥", "answer": "ことり", "english_answer": "little bird" },
        { "question": "白鳥", "answer": "はくちょう", "english_answer": "swan" },
        { "question": "野原", "answer": "のはら", "english_answer": "fields" },
        { "question": "野鳥", "answer": "やちょう", "english_answer": "wild bird" },
        { "question": "分野", "answer": "ぶんや", "english_answer": "genre, area" },
        { "question": "野菜", "answer": "やさい", "english_answer": "vegetable" },
        { "question": "菜食", "answer": "さいしょく", "english_answer": "vegetarian diet" },
        { "question": "青菜", "answer": "あおな", "english_answer": "leafy green vegetable" },
        { "question": "お茶", "answer": "おちゃ", "english_answer": "tea" },
        { "question": "茶色", "answer": "ちゃいろ", "english_answer": "brown" },
        { "question": "喫茶店", "answer": "きっさてん", "english_answer": "coffee shop" },
        { "question": "紅茶", "answer": "こうちゃ", "english_answer": "black tea" },
        { "question": "ご飯", "answer": "ごはん", "english_answer": "cooked rice, meal" },
        { "question": "夕飯", "answer": "ゆうはん", "english_answer": "supper" },
        { "question": "晩ご飯", "answer": "ばんごはん", "english_answer": "supper" },
        { "question": "昼飯", "answer": "ひるめし", "english_answer": "lunch" },
        { "question": "味", "answer": "あじ", "english_answer": "taste" },
        { "question": "意味", "answer": "いみ", "english_answer": "meaning" },
        { "question": "趣味", "answer": "しゅみ", "english_answer": "hobby" },
        { "question": "興味", "answer": "きょうみ", "english_answer": "interest" }
    ],
    "N4L15KQuiz": [
        { "question": "代わる", "answer": "かわる", "english_answer": "take somebody's place" },
        { "question": "代わりに", "answer": "かわりに", "english_answer": "instead" },
        { "question": "時代", "answer": "じだい", "english_answer": "age" },
        { "question": "ガス代", "answer": "ガスだい", "english_answer": "gas charge" },
        { "question": "使う", "answer": "つかう", "english_answer": "to use" },
        { "question": "大使館", "answer": "たいしかん", "english_answer": "embassy" },
        { "question": "使用中", "answer": "しようちゅう", "english_answer": "be engaged on something" },
        { "question": "作る", "answer": "つくる", "english_answer": "to make" },
        { "question": "作文", "answer": "さくぶん", "english_answer": "essay" },
        { "question": "作家", "answer": "さっか", "english_answer": "writer" },
        { "question": "作業", "answer": "さぎょう", "english_answer": "operation" },
        { "question": "変化する", "answer": "へんかする", "english_answer": "to change" },
        { "question": "文化", "answer": "ぶんか", "english_answer": "culture" },
        { "question": "化学", "answer": "かがく", "english_answer": "chemistry" },
        { "question": "映画化", "answer": "えいがか", "english_answer": "making into a movie" },
        { "question": "信じる", "answer": "しんじる", "english_answer": "to believe" },
        { "question": "信号", "answer": "しんごう", "english_answer": "signal" },
        { "question": "自信", "answer": "じしん", "english_answer": "confidence" },
        { "question": "通信", "answer": "つうしん", "english_answer": "correspondence" },
        { "question": "進む", "answer": "すすむ", "english_answer": "to proceed" },
        { "question": "進歩", "answer": "しんぽ", "english_answer": "progress" },
        { "question": "先進国", "answer": "せんしんこく", "english_answer": "advanced nation" },
        { "question": "送る", "answer": "おくる", "english_answer": "to send" },
        { "question": "送金", "answer": "そうきん", "english_answer": "remittance" },
        { "question": "放送", "answer": "ほうそう", "english_answer": "broadcasting" },
        { "question": "送信", "answer": "そうしん", "english_answer": "send (e-mail)" },
        { "question": "返す", "answer": "かえす", "english_answer": "return" },
        { "question": "返事", "answer": "へんじ", "english_answer": "answer" },
        { "question": "返信", "answer": "へんしん", "english_answer": "reply (e-mail)" },
        { "question": "くり返す", "answer": "くりかえす", "english_answer": "to repeat" },
        { "question": "洗う", "answer": "あらう", "english_answer": "to wash" },
        { "question": "手洗い", "answer": "てあらい", "english_answer": "hand wash" },
        { "question": "お手洗い", "answer": "おてあらい", "english_answer": "rest room" },
        { "question": "洗濯", "answer": "せんたく", "english_answer": "washing" },
        { "question": "注意する", "answer": "ちゅういする", "english_answer": "to pay attention" },
        { "question": "注文する", "answer": "ちゅうもんする", "english_answer": "to order" },
        { "question": "注射", "answer": "ちゅうしゃ", "english_answer": "injection" }
    ],
    "N4L16KQuiz": [
        { "question": "場所", "answer": "ばしょ", "english_answer": "place" },
        { "question": "工場", "answer": "こうじょう", "english_answer": "factory" },
        { "question": "広場", "answer": "ひろば", "english_answer": "square" },
        { "question": "運動場", "answer": "うんどうじょう", "english_answer": "playground" },
        { "question": "建てる", "answer": "たてる", "english_answer": "to build" },
        { "question": "建物", "answer": "たてもの", "english_answer": "building" },
        { "question": "建築", "answer": "けんちく", "english_answer": "construction" },
        { "question": "物", "answer": "もの", "english_answer": "thing" },
        { "question": "買い物", "answer": "かいもの", "english_answer": "shopping" },
        { "question": "動物", "answer": "どうぶつ", "english_answer": "animal" },
        { "question": "荷物", "answer": "にもつ", "english_answer": "baggage" },
        { "question": "病院", "answer": "びょういん", "english_answer": "hospital" },
        { "question": "入院する", "answer": "にゅういんする", "english_answer": "to be hospitalized" },
        { "question": "大学院", "answer": "だいがくいん", "english_answer": "graduate school" },
        { "question": "映画館", "answer": "えいがかん", "english_answer": "movie theater" },
        { "question": "大使館", "answer": "たいしかん", "english_answer": "embassy" },
        { "question": "旅館", "answer": "りょかん", "english_answer": "inn" },
        { "question": "美術館", "answer": "びじゅつかん", "english_answer": "art museum" },
        { "question": "食堂", "answer": "しょくどう", "english_answer": "dining room" },
        { "question": "講堂", "answer": "こうどう", "english_answer": "auditorium" },
        { "question": "教室", "answer": "きょうしつ", "english_answer": "classroom" },
        { "question": "地下室", "answer": "ちかしつ", "english_answer": "basement" },
        { "question": "待合室", "answer": "まちあいしつ", "english_answer": "waiting room" },
        { "question": "事務室", "answer": "じむしつ", "english_answer": "office" },
        { "question": "工場", "answer": "こうじょう", "english_answer": "factory" },
        { "question": "工事", "answer": "こうじ", "english_answer": "construction" },
        { "question": "工業", "answer": "こうぎょう", "english_answer": "manufacturing" },
        { "question": "工作", "answer": "こうさく", "english_answer": "handicraft" },
        { "question": "図", "answer": "ず", "english_answer": "figure" },
        { "question": "地図", "answer": "ちず", "english_answer": "map" },
        { "question": "図書館", "answer": "としょかん", "english_answer": "library" },
        { "question": "合図", "answer": "あいず", "english_answer": "signal" },
        { "question": "信号", "answer": "しんごう", "english_answer": "signal" },
        { "question": "電話番号", "answer": "でんわばんごう", "english_answer": "telephone number" },
        { "question": "３号室", "answer": "さんごうしつ", "english_answer": "room No.3" },
        { "question": "号令", "answer": "ごうれい", "english_answer": "command" }
    ],
    "N4L17KQuiz": [
        { "question": "交通", "answer": "こうつう", "english_answer": "traffic" },
        { "question": "交差点", "answer": "こうさてん", "english_answer": "crossing" },
        { "question": "交番", "answer": "こうばん", "english_answer": "police box" },
        { "question": "交代", "answer": "こうたい", "english_answer": "change" },
        { "question": "通る", "answer": "とおる", "english_answer": "to go through" },
        { "question": "通う", "answer": "かよう", "english_answer": "to commute" },
        { "question": "通学", "answer": "つうがく", "english_answer": "commute to school" },
        { "question": "大通り", "answer": "おおどおり", "english_answer": "main street" },
        { "question": "動く", "answer": "うごく", "english_answer": "to move" },
        { "question": "運動", "answer": "うんどう", "english_answer": "exercise" },
        { "question": "自動車", "answer": "じどうしゃ", "english_answer": "car" },
        { "question": "動物", "answer": "どうぶつ", "english_answer": "animal" },
        { "question": "乗る", "answer": "のる", "english_answer": "to get on" },
        { "question": "タクシー乗り場", "answer": "タクシーのりば", "english_answer": "taxi stand" },
        { "question": "乗車券", "answer": "じょうしゃけん", "english_answer": "ticket to ride" },
        { "question": "降りる", "answer": "おりる", "english_answer": "to get off" },
        { "question": "（雨が）降る", "answer": "ふる", "english_answer": "to rain" },
        { "question": "乗り降り", "answer": "のりおり", "english_answer": "get on and get off" },
        { "question": "降雨量", "answer": "こううりょう", "english_answer": "rainfall" },
        { "question": "運ぶ", "answer": "はこぶ", "english_answer": "to transport" },
        { "question": "運がいい", "answer": "うんがいい", "english_answer": "lucky" },
        { "question": "運賃", "answer": "うんちん", "english_answer": "fare" },
        { "question": "運転する", "answer": "うんてんする", "english_answer": "to drive" },
        { "question": "自転車", "answer": "じてんしゃ", "english_answer": "bicycle" },
        { "question": "回転", "answer": "かいてん", "english_answer": "rolling" },
        { "question": "転勤", "answer": "てんきん", "english_answer": "job transfer" },
        { "question": "帰る", "answer": "かえる", "english_answer": "to return" },
        { "question": "帰国する", "answer": "きこくする", "english_answer": "to return one's country" },
        { "question": "お帰りなさい", "answer": "おかえりなさい", "english_answer": "welcome home" },
        { "question": "出発する", "answer": "しゅっぱつする", "english_answer": "to leave" },
        { "question": "発見", "answer": "はっけん", "english_answer": "discovery" },
        { "question": "発明", "answer": "はつめい", "english_answer": "invention" },
        { "question": "発車", "answer": "はっしゃ", "english_answer": "departure" },
        { "question": "着る", "answer": "きる", "english_answer": "to put on clothes" },
        { "question": "着く", "answer": "つく", "english_answer": "to arrive" },
        { "question": "着物", "answer": "きもの", "english_answer": "clothes, kimono" },
        { "question": "着信（メール）", "answer": "ちゃくしん（メール）", "english_answer": "incoming e-mail" }
    ],
    "N4L18KQuiz": [
        { "question": "漢字", "answer": "かんじ", "english_answer": "Chinese character" },
        { "question": "漢方薬", "answer": "かんぽうやく", "english_answer": "Chinese herbal medicine" },
        { "question": "字", "answer": "じ", "english_answer": "letter" },
        { "question": "活字", "answer": "かつじ", "english_answer": "type" },
        { "question": "習字", "answer": "しゅうじ", "english_answer": "calligraphy" },
        { "question": "文", "answer": "ぶん", "english_answer": "sentence" },
        { "question": "文学", "answer": "ぶんがく", "english_answer": "literature" },
        { "question": "文字", "answer": "もじ", "english_answer": "character" },
        { "question": "注文する", "answer": "ちゅうもんする", "english_answer": "to order" },
        { "question": "教える", "answer": "おしえる", "english_answer": "to teach" },
        { "question": "教室", "answer": "きょうしつ", "english_answer": "classroom" },
        { "question": "教科書", "answer": "きょうかしょ", "english_answer": "textbook" },
        { "question": "教会", "answer": "きょうかい", "english_answer": "church" },
        { "question": "勉強する", "answer": "べんきょうする", "english_answer": "to study" },
        { "question": "習う", "answer": "ならう", "english_answer": "to learn" },
        { "question": "練習", "answer": "れんしゅう", "english_answer": "practice" },
        { "question": "復習する", "answer": "ふくしゅうする", "english_answer": "to review" },
        { "question": "習慣", "answer": "しゅうかん", "english_answer": "custom" },
        { "question": "英語", "answer": "えいご", "english_answer": "English" },
        { "question": "英国", "answer": "えいこく", "english_answer": "England" },
        { "question": "英雄", "answer": "えいゆう", "english_answer": "hero" },
        { "question": "考える", "answer": "かんがえる", "english_answer": "to think" },
        { "question": "考古学", "answer": "こうこがく", "english_answer": "archaeology" },
        { "question": "参考書", "answer": "さんこうしょ", "english_answer": "reference book" },
        { "question": "研究する", "answer": "けんきゅうする", "english_answer": "do research" },
        { "question": "研究者", "answer": "けんきゅうしゃ", "english_answer": "researcher" },
        { "question": "研究室", "answer": "けんきゅうしつ", "english_answer": "laboratory" }
    ],
    "N4L19KQuiz": [
        { "question": "問", "answer": "とい", "english_answer": "question" },
        { "question": "問題", "answer": "もんだい", "english_answer": "question" },
        { "question": "質問する", "answer": "しつもんする", "english_answer": "to ask a question" },
        { "question": "題名", "answer": "だいめい", "english_answer": "title" },
        { "question": "宿題", "answer": "しゅくだい", "english_answer": "homework" },
        { "question": "話題", "answer": "わだい", "english_answer": "topic" },
        { "question": "試合", "answer": "しあい", "english_answer": "game" },
        { "question": "試験", "answer": "しけん", "english_answer": "examination" },
        { "question": "入試", "answer": "にゅうし", "english_answer": "entrance exam" },
        { "question": "試す", "answer": "ためす", "english_answer": "to try" },
        { "question": "実験", "answer": "じっけん", "english_answer": "experiment" },
        { "question": "経験", "answer": "けいけん", "english_answer": "experience" },
        { "question": "受験する", "answer": "じゅけんする", "english_answer": "to take an examination" },
        { "question": "質問する", "answer": "しつもんする", "english_answer": "to ask a question" },
        { "question": "品質", "answer": "ひんしつ", "english_answer": "quality" },
        { "question": "間に合う", "answer": "まにあう", "english_answer": "to be in time" },
        { "question": "場合", "answer": "ばあい", "english_answer": "case" },
        { "question": "都合がいい", "answer": "つごうがいい", "english_answer": "convenient" },
        { "question": "答える", "answer": "こたえる", "english_answer": "to answer" },
        { "question": "答え", "answer": "こたえ", "english_answer": "answer" },
        { "question": "解答", "answer": "かいとう", "english_answer": "answer" },
        { "question": "用事", "answer": "ようじ", "english_answer": "business" },
        { "question": "利用する", "answer": "りようする", "english_answer": "to use" },
        { "question": "子ども用", "answer": "こどもよう", "english_answer": "for children" },
        { "question": "使用禁止", "answer": "しようきんし", "english_answer": "Do not use" },
        { "question": "紙", "answer": "かみ", "english_answer": "paper" },
        { "question": "手紙", "answer": "てがみ", "english_answer": "letter" },
        { "question": "コピー用紙", "answer": "コピーようし", "english_answer": "photocopying paper" },
        { "question": "新聞紙", "answer": "しんぶんし", "english_answer": "a piece of newspaper" },
        { "question": "意味", "answer": "いみ", "english_answer": "meaning" },
        { "question": "注意する", "answer": "ちゅういする", "english_answer": "to pay attention" },
        { "question": "用意する", "answer": "よういする", "english_answer": "to prepare" },
        { "question": "意見", "answer": "いけん", "english_answer": "opinion" }
    ],
    "N4L20KQuiz": [
        { "question": "引く", "answer": "ひく", "english_answer": "to pull" },
        { "question": "引き出し", "answer": "ひきだし", "english_answer": "withdraw money" },
        { "question": "引力", "answer": "いんりょく", "english_answer": "gravity" },
        { "question": "開ける", "answer": "あける", "english_answer": "to open" },
        { "question": "開く", "answer": "ひらく", "english_answer": "to open" },
        { "question": "開店", "answer": "かいてん", "english_answer": "opening of shop" },
        { "question": "開始する", "answer": "かいしする", "english_answer": "to start" },
        { "question": "閉める", "answer": "しめる", "english_answer": "to close" },
        { "question": "閉じる", "answer": "とじる", "english_answer": "to close" },
        { "question": "閉館する", "answer": "へいかんする", "english_answer": "to close facilities" },
        { "question": "閉会式", "answer": "へいかいしき", "english_answer": "closing ceremony" },
        { "question": "去年", "answer": "きょねん", "english_answer": "last year" },
        { "question": "過去", "answer": "かこ", "english_answer": "the past" },
        { "question": "消去", "answer": "しょうきょ", "english_answer": "erasing" },
        { "question": "死ぬ", "answer": "しぬ", "english_answer": "to die" },
        { "question": "死者", "answer": "ししゃ", "english_answer": "the dead" },
        { "question": "急死", "answer": "きゅうし", "english_answer": "sudden death" },
        { "question": "病死", "answer": "びょうし", "english_answer": "die of disease" },
        { "question": "集める", "answer": "あつめる", "english_answer": "to collect" },
        { "question": "集まる", "answer": "あつまる", "english_answer": "to gather" },
        { "question": "文集", "answer": "ぶんしゅう", "english_answer": "miscellany" },
        { "question": "集合する", "answer": "しゅうごうする", "english_answer": "to get together" },
        { "question": "知る", "answer": "しる", "english_answer": "to know" },
        { "question": "知り合い", "answer": "しりあい", "english_answer": "acquaintance" },
        { "question": "通知", "answer": "つうち", "english_answer": "notice" },
        { "question": "知識", "answer": "ちしき", "english_answer": "knowledge" },
        { "question": "売る", "answer": "うる", "english_answer": "to sell" },
        { "question": "売店", "answer": "ばいてん", "english_answer": "stand" },
        { "question": "売り場", "answer": "うりば", "english_answer": "counter" },
        { "question": "自動販売機", "answer": "じどうはんばいき", "english_answer": "vending machine" },
        { "question": "説明する", "answer": "せつめいする", "english_answer": "to explain" },
        { "question": "小説", "answer": "しょうせつ", "english_answer": "novel" },
        { "question": "思う", "answer": "おもう", "english_answer": "to think" },
        { "question": "思い出す", "answer": "おもいだす", "english_answer": "to remember" },
        { "question": "思い出", "answer": "おもいで", "english_answer": "memory" },
        { "question": "思想", "answer": "しそう", "english_answer": "thought" }
    ]
}
